[
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The interim government in Germany between WWI and the rise of the Nazi party was known as", "options": ["The Weimar Republic", "The Second Reich", "The Kaiser", "The Directory"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The Aunchluss, or Union, occured in 1938 between two countries?", "options": ["The Soviet Union and Finland", "Germany and Czechloslovakia", "Germany and Austria", "Germany and Japan"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "Von Ribbentrop signed the Non-Aggression pact in 1939 between", "options": ["Germany and Italy", "Germany and the Soviet Union", "Germany and Japan", "Austria and Hungary"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "At the beginning of the war in the Pacific theatre a contingent of U.S. troops under General MacArthur was forced to surrender at", "options": ["Wake Island", "Burma", "Pearl Harbor", "Bataan"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "During the Battle of France the Germans bypassed the Maginot Line by attacking through", "options": ["Norway", "Belgium", "Switzerland", "Italy"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The main battle rifle of the German Army during the war was known as", "options": ["The K98", "The M1 Garand", "The Lebel", "The Mosin-Nagant"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "What fighter plane from WWII has become the most produced fighter in history?", "options": ["The Spitfire", "The P-51 Mustang", "The Messerschmidt 109", "The Mitsubishi Zero"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The German submarine that attempted to strangle the supply lines to Britain was called the", "options": ["Midget Sub", "Seigelflugen", "N-47s", "Unterseebooten"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The Japanese Zero was superior to American fighter aircraft at the beginning of the war in the Pacific", "options": ["True", "False"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "Operation Barbarossa was", "options": ["The Plans for the Invasion of England", "The German invasion of the Soviet Union", "The Battle of the Bulge", "The German rescue of Benito Mussolini"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The prime minister of England prior to Winston Churchill was", "options": ["Chamberlain", "Atley", "Thatcher", "Dowding"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The purpose of the Potsdam Conference was to", "options": ["Establish the policy of unconditional surrender", "Plan the Arctic convoys to the Soviet Union", "Shape post-war Germany", "Attempt to bring the war to a peaceful compromise"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The battle of Leyte Gulf was a naval engagement during this larger battle", "options": ["Guadacanal", "Iwo Jima", "Okinawa", "Midway"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "Italy switched sides during the war", "options": ["True", "False"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The most famous Soviet commander was", "options": ["Khruschev", "Voronov", "Kalashnikov", "Zhukov"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The most famous German gun of the war was the", "options": ["Flak30 20mm", "75mm L70", "Flak36 88mm", "Pak 36 37mm \"Doorknocker\""]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "This man was a member of The Red Baron's fighter squadron and commander of the Luftwaffe during WWII.", "options": ["Von Richtofen", "Hermann Goering", "Reinhard Heydrich", "Erwin Rommel"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The most famous British general of the war was", "options": ["Dowding", "Patton", "Montgomery", "Alexander"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The Supreme Commander of the Western Allied forces was", "options": ["Churchill", "Roosevelt", "Bradley", "Eisenhower"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "Monte Cassino was", "options": ["An Italian General", "An abbey in France", "A former monastery in Italy", "A German recreation town"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The main battle tank of the Soviet Union at the time was the", "options": ["Sevastapool", "T-54", "Stalin", "T-34"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "Jet fighters never flew in operational combat during World War II", "options": ["True", "False"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "What was sister-ship of the German Bismarck battleship?", "options": ["Tirpitz", "Scharnhorst", "Prince Oigen", "Graf Spee"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The premiere divebombing aeroplane of 1940 was known as", "options": ["British Blackburn", "American Corsair", "Germans JU-87 \"Stuka\"", "Soviet IL-2 Sturmovick"]},
{"type": "multiple-choice", "answer": "C", "createdAt": "2023-03-07 22:36:48", "question": "The landings at Anzio were during this campaign", "options": ["Guadacanal", "Sicily", "France", "Italy"]}
]